http://www.sailriders.com/legal.php

Cookies are used on SailRiders to ensure you get the best experience. By using this site you agree to our use of cookies. See our Privacy Policy for more details.
OK
BlogImagesVideosWaypointsAccount
End User Agreement
Please take some time to read the following as it contains important information.
By using this website, you, the user, agree to abide by the terms of this agreement.
1. General Information
The term “SailRiders” in this agreement refers to the SailRiders.com website, and “user” refers to you, the person who is using this service. Please take some time to read and understand our terms and conditions and privacy policy.
SailRiders reserves the right to deny the use of this website to anyone who does not comply with this agreement or uses the website in an inappropriate or unacceptable manner.
The terms of this agreement are subject to change without notice. This agreement supersedes and replaces all previous user agreements.
2. Disclaimer of Warranty
The information on these pages may be out of date, incomplete, or contain errors and is for informational purposes only. It is the user’s responsibility to judge the validity of the information and to decide whether or not to get into contact with other users or to complete a business transaction. Be careful with your dealings over the Internet and about what private information you disclose!
Any information provided directly on this website or indirectly through this website by hypertext link or otherwise is provided “as is” without warranty of any kind whether expressed or implied, including, but not limited to, the implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement.
In no event shall SailRiders be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, special or consequential damages, or damages for loss of profits, revenue, programs, data or use, incurred by you or any third party, whether in contract, tort or otherwise, arising from your access to, use of or the inability to use this website, or reliance upon information obtained from or through this website.
SailRiders reserves the right to make changes, updates, or corrections to the information on this website at any time without notice.
3. Copyright Information and Hyperlinking
The material published on this website, including text and graphics, cannot be mirrored, distributed or used for commercial purposes without the prior agreement of SailRiders. This material can be printed, copied, or stored on your computer for personal use only, but cannot be modified or redistributed, and is protected by Canadian and international copyright laws and conventions.
SailRiders supports the hyperlinking from other websites of the material contained on this website provided that it ensures the consistency and accuracy of the information made available. SailRiders does not warranty the exactness, or completeness of the information contained on this website or any other website.
SailRiders also enables third parties to place ads and hyperlinks on its website for convenience of users. These linked sites and content are not controlled by SailRiders and accessing the third party website is entirely at the user’s risk.
4. Software and Digital Media
Software and
digital media available on this website is available
free of charge, under the property of SailRiders. User may not
reverse engineer, decompile, or disassemble any software, nor attempt to copy, alter or redistribute sofware and digital media from SailRiders.
5. Waypoint Manager
The Waypoint Manager is provided for free use on this
website for informational purposes only and should not be used for real navigation. Up to date, accurate navigational charts should be used and eyeball navigation should be practiced at all times.
SailRiders does not guarantee the accuracy, content, or quality of the information and SailRiders is not responsible for any malfunction of the search tool, incorrect search results, or
results containing unexpected, offensive or damaging content. Furthermore, SailRiders is not responsible for any errors or malfunctions of your GPS device, handheld or computer resulting from the download of data from this website.
6. Maps and Geolocation
Maps on this website are a property of Google. Their use is governed by the Google terms and conditions. SailRiders
provides the waypoint overlay to these maps containing various geographical information pertinent to the user and a search tool to quickly identify the waypoints.
Geolocation is a feature that is only
available per the user's consent. It consists of the identification of the geographic location of a user or computing device via a variety of data collecton mechanisms. SailRiders geolocation service uses network routing addresses or internal GPS device information to determine the users location. Note that geolocation is a device-specific API and that not all browser/devices support it. SailRiders offers no warranty on the precision of the geolocation information.
7. Downloading, Uploading and Collaboration
This database is meant to provide a means for sharing information between users. Information
on waypoints may be provided by any user and
SailRiders cannot guarantee its accuracy, completeness, or validity. The
user is responsible to verify the information before downloading any waypoint from the database.
New and modified waypoints may be monitored for content. It is the user's responsibility to display accurate information about the waypoints including text, links and images. If the information is considered inappropriate or unacceptable, SailRiders reserves the right to make changes to, or delete specific elements of the insereted information, or the information in its entirety.
When uploading to SailRiders (ex. information on a new waypoint), the user
agrees not to upload any copyrighted, offensive or misleading information. Furthermore, the user is required to provide some identifying information. Some of this personal information may be disclosed to the public for reference. Please read our privacy policy for more information on what personal information is disclosed to the public.
Please contact us if you have any additional questions.
